<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personal on Tim Jonas Meinerzhagen</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/tags/personal/</link><description>Recent content in personal on Tim Jonas Meinerzhagen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://timmeinerzhagen.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>dependabot-sha-comment-action</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/dependabot-sha-comment-action/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/dependabot-sha-comment-action/</guid><description>dependabot-sha-comment-action A tool that comments GitHub Actions that are pinned to commits SHAs whenever they are updated via Dependabot.
The Problem with Actions GitHub Actions is a great tool for CI/CD utilizing GitHubs vast community to easily share Actions, which simplify many use cases and integrations vastly.
One major issue of Actions is versioning, which is based on normal git tags. These tags are not immutable, thus attackers could easily delete a tag, introduce malicous code, and add the same tag again - anybody using that tag is now running the malicous code.</description></item><item><title>timmeinerzhagen.com</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/timmeinerzhagen.com/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/timmeinerzhagen.com/</guid><description>timmeinerzhagen.com Personal website, utilized as landing page, overview, as well as general link distribution
Setup This website is build using Hugo with the hugo-coder theme. The entire page is build using GitHub Actions and hosted via GitHub Pages.
Previous versions There were various other iterations of my website through the years.
Here is a short timeline:
Year Hosting Framework Why I Moved away from that 2022 - GitHub Pages Hugo / 2021 - 2022 GCP App Engine React Improve performance, less JavaScript 2020 - 2021 GCP Compute Engine Bootstrap No longer free for public hosting 2018 - 2020 Raspberry Pi with nginx Bootstrap Wanted to try cloud 2016 - 2018 GitHub Pages / Wanted to tinker with Raspberry Pi References See the GitHub project timmeinerzhagen/timmeinerzhagen.</description></item></channel></rss>