<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cloud on Tim Jonas Meinerzhagen</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/tags/cloud/</link><description>Recent content in cloud on Tim Jonas Meinerzhagen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://timmeinerzhagen.com/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>dependabot-sha-comment-action</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/dependabot-sha-comment-action/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/dependabot-sha-comment-action/</guid><description>dependabot-sha-comment-action A tool that comments GitHub Actions that are pinned to commits SHAs whenever they are updated via Dependabot.
The Problem with Actions GitHub Actions is a great tool for CI/CD utilizing GitHubs vast community to easily share Actions, which simplify many use cases and integrations vastly.
One major issue of Actions is versioning, which is based on normal git tags. These tags are not immutable, thus attackers could easily delete a tag, introduce malicous code, and add the same tag again - anybody using that tag is now running the malicous code.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Account Management Tool</title><link>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/cloud-account/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:04:38 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://timmeinerzhagen.com/projects/cloud-account/</guid><description>Cloud Account Management Tool As part of the final project of my appretenticeship program in informatics, focus application development, which I absolved at Bayer, we were required to develop a full fledged application and document the whole process thoroughly.
I finished this project in the cloud team, which needed a single pane of glass that allowed them to get an overview of all cloud accounts and internal metadata for it.</description></item></channel></rss>